

PONJEVIC **GORAN**Web developer

Beograd, Novi Beograd

☑ ponjevic.goran@hotmail.com

& +381 66 166 006

SOCIAL

- in goran-ponjevic
- minnuss /
- goran.ponjevic

PROFILE

Hi, I'm Goran. I have a 10+ years of experience in administration and IT support. I am outgoing, dedicated, open-minded. I believe that a person should work on developing their professional skills and learning new things all the time. Currently, I'm looking for new career opportunities in Web Development.

EDUCATION

Masinski Tehnicar
Tehnička škola "Novi Beograd"
1997 - 2000

SKILLS

- Html
- MS Navision
- CSS
- Ubuntu
- Sass
- JIRA
- JavaScript
- Git
- SEO on page

EXPERIENCE

ADMINISTRATION & IT SUPPORT

From 2005 to 2021 | Fortuna Int.

Worked in MS Dynamics Navision, creating and inserting data (articles, descriptions, customers, manipulating images), processing orders, making offers, taking care of goods logistics.

Analyzing various data and generating reports.

Managing GPS tracking software.

Troubleshooting IT problems, hardware, software, and network related. Installing and maintaining computers and other devices in company.

MILITARY SERVICE

From 2002 to 2003 | Prištinski korpus

Military service in Prištinski korpus, city of Vranje.

PC HARDWARE TRADING

From 2001 to 2002 | Cedens Co.

Selling pc components.

Assembling desktop PCs.

Testing hardware, installing OS, drivers and software.

REFERENCES

Selling natural sweets Music studio

koliko.rs ponksound.rs

Email: quince@koliko.rs Email: info@ponksound.com

Free time tracker Fitness club

Clockify (recreated) gYmantic

Email: /

LANGUAGES

EnglishSerbian

INTERESTS

Music Fitness Movies Technology Networking